<resources>
    <string name="app_name">DummyNews</string>
    <string name="n1">Bird flu scare: Eight birds die in Gwalior zoo in last 48 hours</string>
    <string name="n2">Inferno review: Tom Hanks, Irrfan suffer major burns in this fireball of a film</string>
    <string name="n3">Aamir Khan avoids query on Pak film ban at MAMI</string>
    <string name="n4">New Zealand score first win of tour, defeat India by six runs in 2nd ODI</string>
    <string name="n5">Dharamsala, Pune, Ranchi first-time Test venues for India-Australia series</string>
    <string name="n6">India is Facebook’s top priority, driving engagement to catch up with Google</string>
    <string name="n7">Pakistan violates ceasefire along IB in kathuna; BSF jawan injured </string>
    <string name="n8">Why Apple may be the winner as Androids battle</string>

    <string name="ecnews">In Madhya Pradesh, eight birds have died in Gwalior zoo in the last 48 hours from infection, officials’ state.
        Samples have been sent to veterinary hospital for investigation and Precautionary measures have been taken at the zoo in the
        wake of reports of bird flu from some areas of the country. Meanwhile, National Zoological Park in Delhi,
        which has been closed temporarily, has reported fresh cases of deaths of pelican birds.
        The zoo was shut down on Wednesday after nine birds, including painted storks, ducks and pelicans died of Avian influenza
        at its premises between October 14 and October 17.
    </string>

    <string name="movie2">The Da Vinci Code, and its sequel Angels and Demons (which were both much better films that most give them
        credit for) were unfairly panned upon release. Some of those murmurs about Da Vinci Code getting booed for 15 minutes by
        angry Frenchmen immediately after its Cannes premiere in 2006 are still invoked when reminiscing about notorious cinematic
        disasters. But here’s the thing – and once again, this is something most would agree on – both films have, in the years that
        followed, developed quite an audience at home.
    </string>

    <string name="movie3">Superstar Aamir Khan chose to stay mum on the issue of Pakistani film not being screened at the ongoing
        MAMI festival here and the threats over the release of Karan Johar’s Ae Dil Hai Mushkil. During the opening ceremony of
        the 18th Jio MAMI festival, Aamir was asked to give his opinion on the opposition to screening of Pakistani film and the
        Ae Dil Hai Mushkil controversy, the actor said, “MAMI se poocho”, before walking off. Following the Uri terror attack,
        the MNS has threatened not to allow screening of Johar’s film which features Pakistani actor Fawad Khan.
    </string>

    <string name="sports2">Virat Kohli and Kane Williamson are pivotal for India and New Zealand. If they fail, their teams struggle.
        And if they click, it carries their team to victory. With all focus on New Zealand’s faltering batting unit,
        Williamson showed his class at the Ferozeshah Kotla on Thursday, scoring his eighth ODI century (118) to take New Zealand
        to a fighting total 242, and eventually an exciting six-run win in the second match to level the series 1-1. Kohli failed
        and India’s batting struggled as they lost, handing New Zealand their first ODI victory over India on their home
        turf since Cuttack, 2003.
    </string>

    <string name="sports3">The picturesque Himalayan hill station of Dharamsala will make its debut as a Test venue by hosting the
        finale of a much-anticipated series between India and Australia starting February next year. Dharamsala, which is home to
        the Dalai Lama, is the latest beneficiary of a new drive by the Indian board to take five-day cricket to smaller venues,
        along with Ranchi and Pune, which will also host their first Test matches. The opener of the Border-Gavaskar Trophy 2017
        will be played from February 23-27 in Pune followed by matches in Bengaluru, Ranchi and Dharamsala, India’s board said in
        a statement Friday.
    </string>

    <string name="tech2">Ever tried to find out how many apps Google owns on the Indian Android Play Store? The answer is 114.
        In stark contrast, Facebook owns a measly eight apps including WhatsApp, Instagram and Oculus VR. But why are we
        talking about apps? It is because Facebook says that it doesn’t believe in releasing multiple apps to take over a market
        from competition, but in pushing relevant content and driving engagement. Companies like Facebook, Microsoft, Google have been
        fighting to take the maximum pie as India embarks on its digital journey or data revolution. The country presents itself as
        the new revenue generating region with millions of users coming online for the first time mostly via smartphones.
    </string>

    <string name="news2">JAMMU : A BSF jawan was on Friday injured as Pakistani troops violated ceasefire for the fourth consecutive
        day along the International Vorder in Jammu and kashmir’s Kathua district. BSF troops had on Thursday foiled a major infliation bid in
        the same area by a group of six militants. "Pakistani troops used small arms, automatic weapons and 82 mm mortars bombs to
        target Indian positions,he said. India and Pakistani troops are exchanging fire for past four days in the sector. Pakistani
        troops had yesterday heavily shared areas in Bhimber Gali sector along the LoC in Rajouri district.
    </string>

    <string name="tech1">One man’s loss is another man’s gain. And the gain is much larger if you replace ‘man’ with ‘company’.
        So you cannot blame a clutch of smartphone makers to be licking their lips at Samsung’s misfortune. As the South Korean
        giant decided to scrap the beleaguered Note7 globally, other makers of Android phones are counting their chickens.
        But can they rule out their farm being invaded by Apple’s iOS? “Samsung might be able to pacify a few customers with the
        promise of the S7 Edge, but most of them will move away,” said Vishal Tripathi, research director at Gartner.Other Android
        firms are not seen to be in the same league as Samsung. Kawoosa said it won’t be easy for companies like LG, Huawei, OnePlus,
        or Xiaomi to encroach on Samsung’s turf. “It will take a solid marketing strategy, since there is not enough time left for
        them to come up with a new device just targeted to fill the Note 7 void,” said Kawoosa.
    </string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>
